Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Drink it please, I made it myself.
Hyo Seon said it tastes the same,
but I... Fa...
Fa-Fath...
I wanted to be complimented by my dad.
I did wrong.
Please forgive me, Dad.
Dad...
Forgive me, Dad. I was wrong.
Dad!
Dad... I was wrong.
Please forgive me.
Dad... Dad. Dad!
Dad!
I was wrong.
Episode 11
I've done it again, Goo Hyo Seon. This is how large my contributions to Dae Sung are,
but what are you going to do?
At this rate, it'll all become mine.
But still, will that be all right with you?
My mom is no ordinary person, and I'm her daughter.
There's a chance that I may be worse than my mom.
I'm much smarter than my mom.
Don't let anything happen to you. Even if you do, I won't save you.
I've warned you.
Noona. Noona!
Why?
I'm going somewhere real quick.
Where?
Well...That is...
I'm going for Reserve Forces training.
- Reserve Forces training?
- Yes.
Since there's nothing to do at Do Ga. You don't need me, right?
Be safe and come back.
Noona! You are so bad.
A person is talking to you but, you just turn around and walk away.
Come over here and take a look at this bread (brooch).
Bread?
- It's bread. Doesn't it look like bread?
- Isn't it a crown?
The person who sold it to me said that's what it was. But, it looks like bread to me.
What about it?
As long as you wear this, you won't starve.
What is this? Don't do it.
Please just stay still,
When I'm not here, wear that around..this will protect you,
When you change, make sure you change that too.
If you hang bread on yourself, you'll never starve.
Even all the people around you.
I'm serious.
I've lived my life making sure you won't starve, and you won't believe me?
It's strange, those foolish stubborn words, I want to believe in them,
Believe it.
I'll be back. Eat well, and stay healthy.
Who will read this now?
I'm not sure.
Take it.
Aren't you going?
Monk...
P..pl..please save me, Monk.
Why?
You know where all the ahjusshi's live, right?
What did he say?
How poorly did you treat them that they would act like that?
- They won't come back?
- Never.
- What are you trying to do?
- I have to make the yeast and I need people.
You won't succeed.
You only see them as people who will make the wine.
Did you know that this ahjusshi is our high school classmate Dong Soo's father?
- Dong Soo?
- Yeah, Dong Soo.
The Dong Soo who showed up with a bouquet because he liked you.
Do you know that Dong Soo's grandmother is sick?
Ahjusshi always struggled to make ends meet because he had to buy medicine for their grandmother.
Then Dad would intentionally have Dong Soo's dad have extra responsibility
at the factory and at Do Ga, trying to let him earn a bit extra.
I guess you wouldn't know that either.
After he quit his job at our place, he must have no source of income.
What did you do that would make him say he would never come back?
When the ahjusshi's made a mistake,
Dad was very strict with them, but there a reason
the ahjusshis have worked at our place for over twenty years.
You treated the ahjusshi's as if they were cows or horses,
not as human.
If you're going to go in there thoughtlessly and try to threaten them to come back again without any measures, then quit.
I'm going to ask my uncle.
Because he's very close to the ahjussis.
If my uncle tries and still can't get them to come back, then we'll have to do it by ourselves.
No matter how long it takes,
let's just do it by ourselves.
Tell me everything.
Mr. Jang's mood gets better if you feed him something sweet.
Eon Nyeong's father likes meat. Not pork but beef.
Hyo Seon's great-uncle runs an herbal medicine clinic.
Dong Soo's grandmother knew well about your conditions.
I apologize for my behavior the last time.
I have something to ask you.
Tell me.
What am I to you?
What kind of a question is that?
It's because I'm curious.
What am I to you?
Why would you ask something like that?
I want to know definitely what you think of me.
What do you think of me?
By any chance...
Are you going to abandon me?
Are you going to work diligently to rebuild the winery as much as you can...
And...
then leave?
Are you worried ...
that I'd leave?
Just answer the question you've been asked
and then ask your question.
Are you leaving?
Clinging to our relationship ...
is very tiring.
Even if it's just for a moment, can't you pretend to be a close sister to me?
Can't you promise me that you won't go anywhere?
I've thought about it a lot while standing in Do Ga.
If Do Ga crumbles,
it's the same as Dad crumbling again.
I can't let that happen.
There's no way Do Ga can crumble, but
I don't know what to do, how to do it, and where to start.
No matter how hard I try to figure out the answers, I can't.
I wish someone would just hug me.
But even Mom has become strange.
I'm so lonely.
I think that mom is being like that because she's still in shock.
And that she'll get better as some time has passed.
If I don't think like that, I think I'm going to go insane.
Instead of clinging difficulty to you,
I want to smile along side you.
Because of you.
I would like to feel warm.
Don't cry.
Do you think I intentionally made our relationship one so rocky?
I'm not the kind of person who intends to do that. You know that.
I can't intentionally make a relationship so rocky because I want to,
nor can I intentionally act kind.
That's just how I'm made.
But...
I'll try.
I can't be warm towards you. I can't promise that.
Because I don't know how to be like that.
But...
so that you don't have to feel like you're trying so hard...
I'll try to help that.
For a little while.
Really?
Don't cry.
Don't do this kind of thing.
When I told him I had sinned against two girls,
The monk just said to bow down without any explanation.
Could I be forgiven by bowing?
If only I could be, I can continue to bow until I take my last breath.
But...
Ahjussi.
Please....
Please, open your eyes.
Even at that moment, I put myself first.
Ahjussi.
I begged him to not let me commit this sin.
At that moment, I wasn't even worried about Ahjussi dying.
Please... Please open your eyes.
Ahjussi.
But still...
It's okay.
Oh my goodness. He told me it was okay.
How can it be okay?
How? How?
♫ In the solicitude which wakes me up ♫
♫ when I wake up from an exhausted sleep ♫
♫ because I still remember you smiling ♫
♫ You are the only one who is my person ♫
♫ I am living day after day ♫
♫ In your name when tears appear again, woo ♫
♫ I can't bear it ♫
♫ So I can't laugh ♫
♫ I call out your name again ♫
He's back.
He's smiling.
Come here.
I'm back.
That girl that used to cry so much as to tear her insides.
Come here.
Please come here.
Eun Jo.
Eun Jo
Now, I really...
I can't go to you.
I just can't go.
I can't go anymore.
But...
If only you allow me, I...
I'll...
For you two...
as if bowing 30 million times, I will look after both of you.
Just like Ahjussi.
In place of Ahjussi.
I never
asked you to come to me.
Because I never asked you to come to me,
I won't ask
why you can't.
I can't understand why you're going to take his place or take care of like he would have,
But, I won't ask.
Okay.
Please do that.
I'm fine
but do that for Hyo Seon.
She has so many gaps.
Even as she tears me apart,
she asks me to hug her
like a puppy.
That aggravates me terribly. Really ...
Even though... I don't like her at all,
if I can make her feel warm,
♫  Again today my memory led me astray  ♫
I think I can be forgiven a bit.
If it's possible,
♫  where you can't hold me again  ♫
I'm really going to try to do it.
I really want
♫  Saying I want to see you and hold you again ♫
to be forgiven.
♫  And hold you again while looking at heaven I'm praying  ♫
That's right. Me too.
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if my heart breaks  ♫
On that day, my horrible girl
cried for us and me one last time.
♫  because you are the only one I love  ♫
I did as well. As I detached my bad girl off of me
I cried one last time.
Goodness, my chest. Why do I feel so uncomfortable.
Dad. Dad...
This is gross. Move.
Aren't you going to move?
The soup's getting cold. Hurry up and come eat.
Why is it only 3 of us?
Then how many should there be?
- What are you talking about?
- Be quiet and eat.
- Eat a lot.
- Mom.
I told her to eat alone because I think my chest feeling uncomfortable
if because I've been eating together with her.
What? I cooked this, after sending the kitchen staff away.
She's eating the food I cooked. Am I starving her? I'm just telling her to eat it separately.
Why are you looking at your mother with such horrible eyes? What about this situation can't you stand?
If you don't want to eat, then don't eat.
Joon Soo, go to your sister's room and see if she's there.
Joon Soo. Go and see if your sister is in her room. Okay?
Okay, you evil witch.
No matter how angry you get or glare at it, it'll be no use.
How much more do you want to sin?
Sin? What sin? What sin am I committing?
Goodness, my chest.
Why does my chest feel so damn stuffy?
Hey, go and bring me some water.
If I'm reborn again, I feel like I'll be born as Hyo Seon's mom and that thought horrifies me!
- What?
- Since you and I have sinned so much,
we may be punished in the form of being born as Hyo Seon's mom!
Are you going to bring me water?
Please find Hyo Seon and get her to eat breakfast.
Is that so? Where did she go without having breakfast?
I don't know. Find her and make sure she eats.
What about you? Did you eat?
Feed her, then bring her to Do Ga.
When someone asks you something learn to not ignore the question and answer them back, you brat.
I asked you if you ate, you brat.
You must be hungry, right? The acorn jelly turned out well.
- Eat a lot.
- Enjoy it.
First, leave the loan problem for me to solve.
- How can you?
- Anyway, just leave it to me.
About the repayment deadline, I think we can get an extension.
Even up to just two days ago, the bank said there was no way we could get a loan.
Trust me. There's someone I know.
Because he's hanging on under stipulations I set, there's no strain.
What conditions?
Even more urgent than that is paying back the elders in the family their money.
The problem is that they don't want shares but their money immediately.
Hyo Seon, will you try to talk to them again?
Okay. I'll do that, Oppa. I'll go see them tomorrow.
Be sure to talk about Eun Jo... To the elders.
Tell them that your smart older sister succeeded in making the yeast that tastes exactly like your father's wine.
That your sister can definitely stand in your father's place.
If not anyone else but you tell them about that, it's possible they could change their minds.
What conditions do you mean? On what conditions did you get an extension?
By any chance, do they want more collateral?
That's not possible at all. There is nothing else to add.
Why don't you just leave that to me? Okay?
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
With this... Let's make mixed rice.
- It's going to be delicious.
- Hold this.
Should we add... two bowls of rice?
Put that away. Without any word, we're just going to do this, right?
This looks delicious.
That's enough. Enough.
Let's go. Hurry up, let's go in.
Come on, everybody. Hurry up, let's all go in.
- What do you keep complaining?
- What complaining?
I wasn't either.
- Let's go. Let's all go in.
- Yes, yes.
Let's just forget everything from before.
Yes, you're right.
It's good to be back.
We heard you're going to make the yeast?
What's the problem? Are you not ready to make it again?
This time, what kind will we make? Will we use wheat bran, right? That's better, right?
Wait, I smell sesame oil. Did someone eat mixed rice?
Ahjussis.
Thank you. Thank you.
Uncle, thank you.
Don't think that we were convinced with a few boxes of herbal medicine.
We're not that kind of people.
We're back because you apologized to us. Do you understand?
Okay, okay, okay then. We shouldn't be standing around here like this.
There. Let's take out those curd boxes and do our best to disinfect them.
Let's go. I said to let's go.
- Right, let's go.
- Let's go and get this started.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Oppa, did you go and get the written invocation?
Who will attend the rites now?
Free story
Statement of our conscience! "Dae Seong True Winemakers"
Hello Publisher. This is Hong Gi Jeong.
I enjoyed reading your current issue.
I enjoyed reading it very much.
What has happened? I can't believe you've actually come all the way into my office.
Gi Hoon knowing the actor behind the fraudulent Japanese exports
is not making an issue of it. What do you think the reason is?
Are you and I on the same side?
No.
I don't think you know, so let me tell you something.
The fact that the successor of Hongju Cooperative, Hong Gi Jeong did it.
And also he is the younger sibling that had a different womb
He cannot bring himself to reveal this fact to the two daughters.
What should be done if Gi Hoon were to hold a legal issue with it in court, I had prepared a strong plan.
It seems to be useless.
Is that what you came here to tell me?
The pretty smart one out of the two daughters
had been featured in an financial magazine and researches yeast strains.
In many ways, she seems to be making an effort.
I don't think the story of the two girls is not what you're really trying to say either.
I also don't think it's sudden you started to have interest in that household's two daughters.
Father...
You're really a bad person.
When Gi Hoon's mother collapsed and fell while running after me,
and when I heard later that she died,
You don't know how hard and painful it was for me, do you?
And that... You used that to manipulate Ki Hoon?
I admire you. I will become bad as well.
I'm curious to find out just how much and how bad I can become.
Do you know that?
I'm not sure. That's something the President has been doing all his life.
Who is going to take over his place?
Geez.
The role of a mistress of the house, is quite big in these instances.
Hyo Seon.
Yes, Oppa.
Who do you think should read the invocation?
Let's do what you want to do.
If there is anyone among the people gathered here, who can make such a decision instead of the President,
I believe that would be Hyo Seon.
In my opinion it should be the eldest person at the Daeseong True Cooperative like Hyeong-nim Hye Jin
Goodness! Oh no, that makes no sense at all.
How could I dare?
Well, I could if it were absolutely necessary.
or Vice Dept Lead Kim, his best friend
No, no.
Or maybe we can ask one of the elders of the family.
Think about it first, and decide tomorrow, Hyo Seon.
I want to just decide now.
Will you all accept my decision?
Then...
I want Unni to do it.
I want Unni to do the yeast ritual ceremony.
Does that make any sense?
That's really ridiculous.
Please do it for us.
Stop insisting. How could I dare do it?
It's the winery's most important event.
I also think that the same way, Unni.
I can't imagine anyone else other than Dad doing it.
But...
I think Dad would be really happy to see you do it.
It's also hard for me to say this.
Why is it you, but not me?
But if Dad had to pick someone to do the ritual for him,
it would be you, Unni.
So Unni, please do it.
You guys said you would accept my decision, didn't you?
Hyo Seon has made her decision, everyone.
The thing is that... I have something to say.
As you know, even though I caused some trouble last time,
this time, the workers...
calling them back in was no easy task.
If not for me, you wouldn't be able to ferment the yeast
or even process it all properly.
Since it was me, I was able to bring them back.
If not for me, there would've been no chance.
What exactly do you want to say to me?
You waited for me to tell me this?
There's nothing else you want to talk to me about?
How can people be so straight-forward?
You have to prepare the story and build up, naturally transitioning into the point-
You've already prepared lots.
Just get straight to the point of your story, I don't have much time.
Your mom keeps telling me to leave.
She told you to leave?
As you know, there's nowhere else I can go if I leave.
I've spent my whole life growing my roots here.
Even if you consider us rocks, I'm the one that's been embedded here, and your mother's the one that rolled in.
No matter how pitiful my circumstances are after my noona passed so suddenly,
- I used to be the prince ...
- I understand. You don't have to leave.
I'll talk to Mom...
I'll talk to her about it, so don't worry. Have a good night.
I already said no! Why are you like this?
What happened?
Mom says her chest feels tight,
so I thought it would be good for her to have some wine.
It eases fatigue and is good for digestion, so...
it's good to drink some to help indigestion.
Get out now! I don't want to see your face!
Hyo Seon, get up.
Get up! Quickly!
Follow me.
MMM
Don't sleep yet. Don't sleep and go out to the pavillion.
I'll send Hyo Seon there in a bit. Comfort her.
What—
Just sit anywhere.
Why do you always get close to Mom? You get hurt every time, so why?
Why are you so obsessed with her?
Don't you know there's something wrong with Mom?
She can't believe that she's become a widow so suddenly,
she's not only acting cold towards you, but everyone in this house!
Just avoid her for a while. Stay away from for a little while.
I...
I can't do that.
What did you say?
I'm always curious about Mom,
and I always miss her.
I keep thinking back to
when Mom pat my head,
when she helped me get a splinter out,
and when she helped me clip my toenails.
Mom is being like this because she's lonely, and I'm lonely too.
So I feel it would be good for us to be together. Even if she hates me for now,
maybe she'll like me again if we see each other often.
Are you an idiot?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
I'm begging you.
Avoid Mom for now.
Eat breakfast with me at the winery,
and work till late with me until Mom is asleep.
If you hide from her like this for a bit, things may get better soon.
Things may get better soon?
Yes.
Do you think I'm a child?
At some point, I also
understood a little.
I knew that Mom treated me differently
when Dad wasn't watching.
I knew it,
but it didn't matter to me.
As much as I was sad about Mom doing that,
I liked her just as much.
As long as I like her,
it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter. Because I like your mother.
You said things will get better if I hide for a while?
It's okay if things don't get better.
It's okay if I'm despised forever.
As long as I'm not kicked out, or you and Mom don't run off,
I'll be okay.
Without you, Mom and Joon Soo,
I'll be alone.
Just don't abandon me.
Don't give up on me.
If you can do that, I'll be grateful.
I'm begging you. Please treat Hyo Seon well, Mom.
That useless girl, Hyo Seon told you to come tell me this?
To tell me to treat her well?
It makes me shudder thinking about how I fawned over her for eight years.
Now what is she saying? Treat her well?
How am I supposed to treat her well? Should I be her hands and feet?
You little wretch. I was never even your hands and feet.
Do I act as Joon Soo's hands and feet?
You and I... it wouldn't be enough if we bowed at Hyo Seon's feet every single day.
What? Do what, where?
Hyo Seon is like her father.
Do you really think Hyo Seon's father didn't know anything?
The fact that you didn't truly like him, that you wouldn't be with him
if he had nothing that you were after,
That you were acting slick like the tongue in your mouth was an act.
You think he didn't know at all?
You think Hyo Seon's father didn't know?
He knew it all.
Even so, he loved you.
It wouldn't be enough even if you were thrown into hell, Mom.
Hyo Seon's father loved someone like that.
When are you going to finish mumbling?
Just like her father,
Hyo Seon said it's okay even if you don't love her.
She doesn't care as long as she loves you.
Mom, where can you find a father like that?
Where can you find a daughter like that?
Mom, where else can you find people like that in this world?
Exactly. How could there be such stupid people in this world?
Mom! Mom!
We can't be like this!
We aren't humans if we do this!
Mom, have a change of heart please!
If we go on like this,
I feel like we'll get struck by lightning anytime, even if we're just walking on the streets.
Why would we get struck by lightning? What did we do wrong?
How can things get worse from here? Why would we get struck by lightning now?
They made me a widow! What right do they have to strike me with lightning?
Why should I be struck by lightning? Why should I be punished again?
If she goes somewhere and we marry her off, I've done all I needed to so I'm tolerating it.
If she doesn't want to see me, tell her to just marry herself off to some guy! Got it?
I wish someone had steamed her like bossam that bitch.
What are you doing?
Let's go. We can't be like this.
We are jinxes to this family.
Wherever we go, we are jinxes.
We'll end up causing a fire somewhere.
We can't do this to this family. We can't stay here.
Let's pack our things.
- Get yourself together, you brat!
- I said to pack up!
Why should we go?
You, me and Joon Soo together is three times more than what Hyo Seon will inherit.
Even though the business is in ruins, there should be something left after everything is settled.
After I get what I want, I'll leave on my own even if you don't insist on it.
Come to your senses, and try to get as much of it as you can.
Let go of my hand.
Listen up. Be smart, you brat.
Now that things have come to this, we have to get ready for what's to come.
Let go of my hand! Let go!
Has this brat lost her mind? Huh?
Get yourself together, got it?!
What happened?
What's wrong?
Can you...
Can you take me and run away somewhere?
It's okay if I can't be forgiven.
No. I won't accept any forgiveness.
So... let's run away. Run away with me.
Let's run away!
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt.
I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
Do you not know what kind of person I am? Do I look like a pushover to you? Didn't I say not to get close to me?
I really miss Dad. I miss him to death.
Noona.
Before Father can tell them, I'll tell them myself and end it.
Eun Jo!
♫ Can't you hear my voice? ♫